Hello, everyone.
大家好。
Welcome back to another lesson with us here at EnglishPod.
欢迎回到 EnglishPod 的又一堂课。
My name is Marco.
我是 Marco。
My name is Catherine and that's us.
我是 Catherine，这就是我们。
And that's us.
这就是我们。
And today we're going to talk about a very common situation when you're a couple, when
今天我们要讨论一个非常常见的情况，当你们是情侣时，当
you have a girlfriend.
你有女朋友时。
Honey, come on.
亲爱的，快点。
I want to go.
我想走了。
Are you?
是吗？
You are taking forever.
你磨蹭太久了。
All right.
好吧。
Who takes long?
谁磨蹭？
Like do you take a long time to get ready, to get dressed?
比如你准备、穿衣服要花很长时间吗？
Okay.
好的。
I take longer to get ready, but my boyfriend takes longer in general because he's like
我准备的时间更长，但我男朋友总体上花的时间更长，因为他就像
checking his email, playing video games, like just, you know, we call it lollygagging.
在查邮件、打游戏，就像，你知道，我们称之为磨蹭。
He's just like being kind of slow.
他就是有点慢吞吞的。
I'm the opposite.
我正好相反。
I usually start getting ready later.
我通常开始准备得比较晚。
Like if we have to leave at nine, I'll start getting ready at 830, but I'll be ready by
比如如果我们得九点出发，我会八点半开始准备，但九点就能准备好，因为
nine because I take a shower real fast, get dressed, and I know what I'm going to wear
我洗澡很快，穿好衣服，而且我知道要穿什么，
and all my clothes are ready.
所有衣服都准备好了。
On the other hand, my girlfriend takes forever to get ready and she's like, oh, and then,
另一方面，我女朋友准备起来要花很长时间，她就像，哦，然后，
you know, the hair.
你知道，头发。
Girls have makeup and tights and shoes.
女生有化妆品、紧身裤和鞋子。
But this is what I understand.
但这就是我理解的。
If we're supposed to leave at nine, why don't you start getting ready before?
如果我们应该九点出发，你为什么不提前开始准备呢？
Never underestimate women.
永远别低估女人。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Procrastination.
拖延症。
Hey, it's not even about procrastination.
嘿，这甚至不是拖延症的问题。
Sometimes it just takes longer to look good than other times.
有时候要打扮好看就是比其他时候花更长时间。
Right.
对。
Well, in this case, we're going to be looking at a lesson where it's the opposite.
嗯，在这个案例中，我们要看的一课正好相反。
The husband is taking a long time to get ready and well, I don't think he has a very good
丈夫准备要花很长时间，而且，嗯，我觉得他没什么好的
fashion sense, right?
时尚感，对吧？
He does not.
他没有。
And we're going to learn what that phrase means in a minute here.
我们马上就会学到那个短语是什么意思。
But before we get going, I've got a couple of words to preview to help you understand
但在开始之前，我有几个词要预览一下，帮助你们理解
what's going on in today's dialogue.
今天对话的内容。
Vocabulary preview.
词汇预览。
All right.
好的。
So, vocabulary preview.
那么，词汇预览。
Today we have two words.
今天有两个词。
The first one can be a noun or a verb, to iron.
第一个可以是名词或动词，熨烫。
Or iron.
或者熨斗。
So to iron basically means to...
所以熨烫基本上意思是……
To get the wrinkles out of clothes.
把衣服上的褶皱弄平。
And so we use this...
所以我们用这个……
Iron is actually a metal.
熨斗实际上是一种金属。
It's a very important metal.
它是一种非常重要的金属。
And an iron is a machine that we plug in.
而熨斗是我们插电用的机器。
We use it to get the wrinkles, the lines out of our shirts and our skirts and everything.
我们用它来弄平衬衫、裙子等上面的褶皱和线条。
So, it's actually a very important thing to make sure that you look nice and put together.
所以，这确实是确保你看起来整洁得体的重要事情。
Right.
对。
So, you use an iron to iron your shirt or to iron your skirt.
所以，你用熨斗来熨衬衫或熨裙子。
And then we have sandals.
然后我们有凉鞋。
My favorite type of shoe.
我最喜欢的鞋类。
Mine too.
我也是。
Sandals.
凉鞋。
I have a friend who used to say she had claustrophobic feet.
我有个朋友以前说她有幽闭恐惧的脚。
Her feet didn't like to be in closed spaces.
她的脚不喜欢待在封闭空间里。
So, she only wore sandals.
所以她只穿凉鞋。
So these are open shoes, open toe shoes basically.
所以这些是开放式鞋子，基本上是露趾鞋。
You wear them at the beach.
你在海滩上穿它们。
Or you wear them in the summer in general.
或者一般在夏天穿。
I'm wearing sandals right now.
我现在就穿着凉鞋。
And you have different types of sandals like sandals and flip-flops, right?
而且有不同类型的凉鞋，比如凉鞋和人字拖，对吧？
Flip-flops I think they're called that because they sound like flip-flop, flip-flop when
人字拖我觉得它们这么叫是因为走路时会发出啪嗒啪嗒的声音，
you walk.
啪嗒啪嗒。
Alright, so those are our two words today.
好了，这就是今天的两个词。
Let's listen to the dialogue for the first time and then we'll be back.
让我们第一次听对话，然后回来。
Honey, come on.
亲爱的，快点。
We're going to be late.
我们要迟到了。
Honestly, you take longer getting ready than I do.
说实话，你准备的时间比我还长。
I was drying my hair and ironing my shirt.
我刚才在吹头发和熨衬衫。
Can you come here for a second?
你能过来一下吗？
I need your help.
我需要你帮忙。
What is it?
什么事？
Why are all these clothes on the bed?
为什么床上全是这些衣服？
I don't know what to wear.
我不知道穿什么。
Okay, give me your opinion.
好吧，给我你的意见。
Do you like the way this looks?
你喜欢这样穿的样子吗？
The striped short-sleeved shirt with this checkered sweater and my lucky sandals.
条纹短袖衬衫配这件格子毛衣和我的幸运凉鞋。
I like the cut and hemline of these shorts.
我喜欢这条短裤的剪裁和底边。
So I think I'll wear these as well.
所以我想我也穿这条。
Are you joking?
你在开玩笑吗？
What am I going to do with you?
我该拿你怎么办？
You're going to a dinner party, not to the beach.
你要去参加晚宴，不是去海滩。
Wear the shirt with the silk tie I bought you and those corduroy pants.
穿我买给你的那件衬衫配那条丝质领带和那条灯芯绒裤子。
It's chilly outside so you can wear this coat.
外面有点凉，所以你可以穿这件外套。
Thanks, honey.
谢谢，亲爱的。
You have such great fashion sense.
你真有很好的时尚感。
Now what am I going to do with my hair?
现在我的头发该怎么办？
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So interesting, this husband sounded a lot like a famous president, I think.
真有趣，这个丈夫听起来很像一位著名的总统，我觉得。
He did, but we'll get to that in a minute.
确实像，但我们一会儿再谈这个。
Before we do talk about who this guy is, I think it'd be a great idea to talk about some
在我们讨论这个人是谁之前，我觉得最好先谈谈一些
of these clothing terms because they're very useful for when you want to go shopping and
这些服装术语，因为当你去购物和
for when you're getting dressed.
穿衣服时它们非常有用。
Language takeaway.
语言要点。
Okay, so the first word that we have on language takeaway is striped.
好的，所以语言要点的第一个词是条纹的。
All right, you might have heard of the American flag called stars and stripes.
好的，你可能听说过美国国旗被称为星条旗。
Stripes are those lines on clothing or on flags that go up or down or left and right.
条纹是衣服或旗帜上那些上下或左右排列的线条。
Exactly.
没错。
So if you have a striped shirt, you have many lines on your shirt that are going up and
所以如果你有一件条纹衬衫，你的衬衫上有很多上下或左右
down or left and right.
排列的线条。
Right, and they say with fashion, lines that go left to right make you look fatter and
对，而且时尚界说，左右排列的线条让你看起来更胖，
lines that go up and down make you look thinner.
上下排列的线条让你看起来更瘦。
And taller.
更高。
Very good.
很好。
And now moving on, if it's summer and you want to wear a shirt, you can wear a short
现在继续，如果是夏天你想穿衬衫，你可以穿一件短
sleeved shirt.
袖衬衫。
All right, this is important.
好的，这很重要。
So most people like to wear short sleeved shirts in the summertime because they're cooler.
所以大多数人喜欢在夏天穿短袖衬衫，因为它们更凉爽。
And in the wintertime, that means we like to wear long sleeved shirts.
而在冬天，这意味着我们喜欢穿长袖衬衫。
Okay, so the sleeves are basically the arms of the shirt.
好的，所以袖子基本上就是衬衫的胳膊部分。
Exactly.
没错。
You say short sleeved.
你说的是短袖。
Very good.
很好。
And then we have a checkered shirt or a checkered sweater in this case.
然后我们这里有一件格子衬衫，或者在这个例子中是格子毛衣。
Okay, so checkered means there are little squares on the shirt and usually one square
好的，所以“checkered”意思是衬衫上有小方块，通常一个方块
is one color and the next square is another color.
是一种颜色，下一个方块是另一种颜色。
So it looks like a checkerboard.
所以它看起来像棋盘。
Very good.
很好。
That game, you know, checkers.
就是那个游戏，你知道的，跳棋。
Or like a chessboard.
或者像国际象棋棋盘。
Exactly.
没错。
And so in this case, we've got a guy who's trying to wear a striped shirt and a checkered
所以在这个例子中，有个人想穿条纹衬衫和格子
sweater.
毛衣。
That does not go well together, right?
这两样搭配起来不好看，对吧？
No.
不好看。
Too much stuff happening.
太乱了。
It's too busy.
太花哨了。
Too busy.
All right.
好吧。
And not only that, but he wanted to wear shorts because he liked the cut and the hemline.
不仅如此，他还想穿短裤，因为他喜欢它的剪裁和底边。
Okay, these are actually terms that we normally use with women's clothing because you could
好的，这些词我们通常用在女装上，因为你可以
say, I like the cut of this dress.
说，我喜欢这条裙子的剪裁。
I like the shape that it has.
我喜欢它的形状。
Very good.
很好。
So the hemline is the bottom of your skirt or your trousers or your shorts and hemline,
所以“hemline”是指裙子、裤子或短裤的底边，关于底边，
we could say, my mother used to say this to me, the hemline is much too high, much too
我们可以说，我妈妈以前常对我说，这底边太高了，太
short.
短了。
That skirt is not appropriate.
那条裙子不合适。
Yeah.
是啊。
So it's nice to have a hemline at the knee.
所以底边在膝盖处挺好的。
All right.
好吧。
So the cut is the shape that the piece of clothing has like pants or skirts and the
所以“cut”是指衣服的形状，比如裤子或裙子，而
hemline would be the place where it ends, right?
“hemline”是指衣服结束的地方，对吧？
The skirt, for example.
比如裙子。
Like it pretty much tells you the length of something.
它基本上告诉你某件东西的长度。
Very good.
很好。
And now the wife steps in, she's like, no, no, you're not wearing this.
现在妻子插话了，她说，不，不，你不能穿这个。
She's telling him that she has to wear nice clothes and among those items is a silk tie.
她告诉他必须穿好看的衣服，其中一件是丝绸领带。
Okay.
好的。
So a classic Father's Day gift.
所以是经典的父亲节礼物。
Silk tie.
丝绸领带。
I've given this one a couple of times.
我送过几次这个。
A silk tie is a necktie, a long necktie that's made of silk.
丝绸领带是一种领带，一种用丝绸做的长领带。
Silk is a very soft material, right?
丝绸是一种非常柔软的材料，对吧？
Very expensive as well.
也非常贵。
It can be, especially Italian silk.
可能很贵，尤其是意大利丝绸。
And I've always actually wanted to have silk sheets.
我一直想要丝绸床单。
Ooh, see, I don't know.
哦，这个嘛，我不确定。
I feel like they would get very warm in the summer.
我觉得夏天会太热。
Yeah.
是啊。
Well, in the winter it would be awesome, but probably very cold in the winter as well.
嗯，冬天会很棒，但可能冬天也很冷。
Yeah.
是啊。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Well, it's one of those things.
嗯，就是那种东西。
And then she's also telling him to wear some corduroy pants.
然后她还让他穿灯芯绒裤子。
Okay.
好的。
So it sounds like this might be a winter dialogue because corduroy is not something you wear
所以听起来这可能是冬天的对话，因为灯芯绒不是夏天穿的
in the summer because it's very heavy and thick.
东西，因为它很厚重。
Corduroy actually is a fabric that usually has these kind of ribs or ridges.
灯芯绒实际上是一种通常有这些棱纹或条纹的面料。
And so there's like little lines in the fabric that make it quite thick and rough when you...
所以面料上有一些细线，让它摸起来很厚实粗糙。
Almost not rough, but they make it feel very unique when you touch it.
几乎不算粗糙，但摸起来很独特。
Yeah.
是啊。
It's not smooth.
它不光滑。
It's a little bit rough, the fabric.
这种面料有点粗糙。
Very good.
很好。
So those are all the clothing items that we've looked at today.
所以这些就是我们今天看的所有衣物。
There's a lot of them.
有很多。
And obviously we'll post a couple of pictures on the site so you can see better what a silk
显然我们会在网站上贴一些图片，这样你可以更好地看到丝绸领带
tie looks like or especially corduroy pants.
是什么样子，尤其是灯芯绒裤子。
Corduroy, yeah.
灯芯绒，是啊。
All right.
好吧。
So let's listen to this dialogue again.
那么让我们再听一遍这段对话。
We're going to slow it down a little bit and then we'll come back and look at some of the
我们会放慢一点速度，然后回来看看一些
phrases.
短语。
Honey, come on.
亲爱的，快点。
We're going to be late.
我们要迟到了。
Honestly, you take longer getting ready than I do.
说实话，你准备的时间比我还长。
I was drying my hair and ironing my shirt.
我刚才在吹头发和熨衬衫。
Can you come here for a minute?
你能过来一下吗？
I'm not ready.
我还没准备好。
I'm here for a sec.
我过来一下。
I need your help.
我需要你帮忙。
What is it?
怎么了？
Why are all these clothes on the bed I don't know what to wear.
为什么床上全是衣服，我不知道穿什么。
Okay, give me your opinion.
好吧，给我你的意见。
Do you like the way this looks the strap short sleeve shirt with this checkered sweater?
你觉得这件条纹短袖衬衫配这件格子毛衣好看吗？
My lucky sandals I like the cut in hemline of these shorts.
我的幸运凉鞋，我喜欢这条短裤的剪裁和底边。
So I think I'll wear these as well.
所以我想我也穿这个。
Are you joking?
你在开玩笑吗？
What am I going to do with you
我该拿你怎么办？
Wear the shirt with the silk tie I bought you and those corduroy pants.
穿我给你买的丝绸领带衬衫和那条灯芯绒裤子。
It's chilly outside, so you can wear this coat.
外面有点凉，所以你可以穿这件外套。
Thanks, honey.
谢谢，亲爱的。
You have such great fashion sense.
你的时尚品味真好。
Now, what am I going to do with my hair?
现在，我的头发该怎么办？
Alright, we're back, so now let's start with Fluency Builder.
好了，我们回来了，现在开始看流利度提升部分。
Fluency Builder.
流利度提升。
OK, these are classic couple phrases, right?
好的，这些都是经典的情侣用语，对吧？
These are phrases you hear among couples, and the first one is maybe more common to
这些是情侣之间常听到的短语，第一个可能更常见于
hear from the female end, but it's not unknown on the male end.
女性，但男性也会用。
So, we have this question.
所以，我们有这个问题。
Do you like the way this looks?
你喜欢这样看起来怎么样？
So while the person is saying this, they would maybe be moving to the side a little bit.
所以当有人说这句话时，他们可能会稍微侧身。
Modeling it.
展示一下。
Do you like the way this looks?
你喜欢这样看起来怎么样？
So basically you're saying, do you like what I'm wearing?
所以基本上你在说，你喜欢我穿的衣服吗？
Does it look good on me?
我穿起来好看吗？
Does it look good?
好看吗？
Exactly.
没错。
You could also say, hey, I like the way this looks when you're trying to buy something
你也可以说，嘿，我喜欢这样看起来怎么样，当你在商店里想买
at the store.
东西的时候。
And so, do you like the way this looks is a way for you to ask the other person's opinion
所以，“你喜欢这样吗”是一种询问对方对你外表看法的方式。
of how you look.
关于你的外表。
And also, another common phrase, especially with men who have no fashion sense, the wife
还有一个常见的短语，尤其是对没有时尚感的男人，妻子会说：“我该拿你怎么办？”
says, what am I going to do with you?
妻子说：“我该拿你怎么办？”
OK, this is an interesting phrase and it needs some explanation, I think, because the meaning
好的，这个短语很有趣，我觉得需要解释一下，因为它的意思是，嗯，这很难办，对吧？
is, well, this is very difficult, right?
所以，你很难搞，或者，哇，你需要我的帮助。
So you're being difficult or, wow, you need some help from me.
你需要我的帮助。
I'm going to help you.
我来帮你。
How am I going to help you this much or all the time like this?
我该怎么帮你这么多，或者一直这样帮你？
Right, because she's pretty much saying he has no idea about clothing and fashion.
对，因为她基本上是在说他完全不懂衣服和时尚。
So he's saying to her, what am I going to do with you?
所以他对她说：“我该拿你怎么办？”
It means you need so much help.
意思是你需要太多帮助了。
Seriously.
真的。
All right.
好吧。
And the third phrase that we saw and we said at the very beginning is fashion sense.
我们一开始看到的第三个短语是“时尚感”。
OK, so this is actually what the man needs help with.
好的，这其实就是这个男人需要帮助的地方。
He needs help with his fashion sense because he has zero fashion sense.
他需要帮助提升时尚感，因为他完全没有时尚感。
And this is pretty much a way to say how much someone knows about fashion or appearances.
这基本上是一种说法，用来表示一个人对时尚或外表了解多少。
And so I can say, oh, my friend Kathy, she has amazing fashion sense.
所以我可以这样说：“哦，我的朋友凯西，她的时尚感超棒。”
So she always looks good.
所以她总是穿得很好看。
Right.
对。
So combining colors appropriately or wearing the right types of shoes with the right types
所以，恰当地搭配颜色，或者穿对鞋子配对衣服等等，这就是时尚感。
of clothing, et cetera, fashion sense.
时尚感。
Or even just being able to wear things that are good on her or telling other people what's
甚至只是能穿适合自己的衣服，或者告诉别人什么适合他们。
good on them.
什么适合他们。
So fashion sense is the ability to identify fashion and look good and make other people
所以时尚感就是识别时尚、让自己好看、也让别人好看的能力。
look good.
让别人也好看。
All right.
好吧。
Very good.
非常好。
Let's listen to this dialogue for the very last time and we'll come back and talk a little
让我们最后一次听这段对话，然后回来再聊一点关于时尚的话题，因为这是个很有趣的话题。
bit more about fashion because it's a very interesting topic.
是的。
It is.
Honey, come on.
亲爱的，快点。
We're going to be late.
我们要迟到了。
Honestly, you take longer getting ready than I do.
说实话，你准备的时间比我还长。
I was drying my hair and ironing my shirt.
我刚才在吹头发和熨衬衫。
Can you come here for a sec?
你能过来一下吗？
I need your help.
我需要你帮忙。
What is it?
怎么了？
Why are all these clothes on the bed?
为什么床上全是衣服？
I don't know what to wear.
我不知道穿什么。
OK, give me your opinion.
好吧，给我你的意见。
Do you like the way this looks?
你喜欢这样穿吗？
The striped short sleeve shirt with this checkered sweater, my lucky sandals.
条纹短袖衬衫配这件格子毛衣，还有我的幸运凉鞋。
I like the cut and hemline of these shorts.
我喜欢这条短裤的剪裁和裤脚边。
So I think I'll wear these as well.
所以我想我也穿这条。
Are you joking?
你在开玩笑吗？
What am I going to do with you?
我该拿你怎么办？
We're going to a dinner party, not to the beach.
我们要去参加晚宴，不是去海滩。
Wear the shirt with the silk tie I bought you and these corduroy pants.
穿我买给你的那件衬衫配丝质领带，还有这条灯芯绒裤子。
It's chilly outside so you can wear this coat.
外面有点冷，所以你可以穿这件外套。
Thanks, honey.
谢谢，亲爱的。
You have such great fashion sense.
你的时尚感真好。
Now, what am I going to do with my hair?
现在，我的头发该怎么办？
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
You lived in Italy for a while.
你在意大利住过一段时间。
How is the fashion over there?
那边的时尚怎么样？
Is it extreme like we see on the runways?
像我们在T台上看到的那样极端吗？
Because I honestly don't understand fashion.
因为我真的不懂时尚。
Well, the thing about runways is that that's not how normal people dress.
嗯，关于T台，那并不是普通人穿衣服的方式。
Well, yeah, that's what I understand.
嗯，对，我明白。
Why do they have these fashion shows if people don't really buy these types of clothing?
如果人们不真的买这些衣服，为什么还要办这些时装秀？
Well, sometimes people like stores, for example, big stores, department stores will buy fashions
嗯，有时候像商店，比如大商店、百货公司，会从T台上买下时装款式。
off of the runway and they'll kind of change them a little bit so that they're more appropriate
然后他们会稍微改一下，让它们更适合普通消费。
for normal consumption.
适合普通消费。
That means for normal people who want to wear them.
也就是说，适合想穿它们的普通人。
But the runway fashions are actually, they're kind of like exaggerations of trends that
但T台时装实际上有点像对购物界、商业界即将出现的潮流的夸张表现。
will happen in the shopping world, right, in the commercial world.
在商业界。
So the things that you see are like big, blown up exaggerations.
所以你看到的东西就像被放大的夸张版。
And we take bits and pieces of those in our daily lives to dress up.
我们在日常生活中会借鉴其中的一些元素来打扮自己。
So different colors or fabrics or like oftentimes you see kind of military outfits.
比如不同的颜色或面料，或者经常能看到一些军装风格的服装。
And so that will translate into military jackets that are very popular one season.
然后这就会转化为某个季节非常流行的军装夹克。
And so Italy definitely counts as a very fashionable country, but it's not crazy.
所以意大利绝对算是一个很时尚的国家，但并没有那么疯狂。
Well, every once in a while you see some more crazy clothes, but I think Japan is much more
嗯，偶尔你会看到一些更疯狂的衣服，但我觉得日本在风格上要疯狂得多。
crazy as far as style.
日本在风格上要疯狂得多。
Yeah, actually, yeah.
是的，确实，是的。
Asian countries such as Japan or South Korea, they have very, also unique fashion as well,
像日本或韩国这样的亚洲国家，它们也有非常独特的时尚。
but it's very extreme to a certain point.
但在某种程度上非常极端。
And the color combinations they do is like red sneakers with green pants and like a blue
它们的颜色搭配，比如红色运动鞋配绿色裤子，再加一件蓝色夹克。
jacket.
蓝色夹克。
It's very crazy.
非常疯狂。
Right.
对。
And very bright.
而且非常鲜艳。
And you often see these shoes, you know, we call them platform shoes.
你经常看到这种鞋，我们叫它厚底鞋。
It's kind of like you're standing on a brick.
就像站在一块砖头上。
Yeah, they're huge.
是的，它们很大。
And they're, you know, they're seven inches tall.
而且，你知道，有七英寸高。
And you see these little girls wearing these big shoes.
你会看到这些小女孩穿着这么大的鞋。
And I just, I'm so scared when I see them because I feel like they're going to fall
我看到她们时真的很害怕，因为我觉得她们会摔倒。
over.
摔倒。
The other thing is that fashion is so expensive.
另一件事是时尚太贵了。
If you actually want to buy something that's in like an authentic, I don't know, Carolina
如果你真想买一件正宗的，比如，我不知道，卡罗琳娜·埃雷拉或奥斯卡·德拉伦塔之类的。
Herrera or Oscar de la Renta or something like that.
奥斯卡·德拉伦塔之类的。
It's so expensive.
太贵了。
It is.
是的。
But you know, high fashion is expensive.
但你知道，高级时装很贵。
Fashion is not, doesn't have to be.
时尚不一定非得贵。
You can be fashionable just looking at different stores and going to secondhand shops and making
你可以通过逛不同的商店、去二手店，甚至自己做衣服来变得时尚。
your own clothes.
自己做衣服。
I mean, it's all about a sense of personal style and dressing yourself to be unique.
我的意思是，这完全关乎个人风格感，以及把自己打扮得独特。
Or you can get at the fake market.
或者你可以去假货市场买。
Or you can go to the fake market.
或者你可以去假货市场。
Exactly.
没错。
All right.
好吧。
That's all the time we have for today, guys.
各位，今天的时间就到这里了。
I hope you enjoyed this lesson.
希望你们喜欢这节课。
Please come to our website and comment at EnglishPod.com.
请来我们的网站，在EnglishPod.com上留言。
And if you have any other suggestions or maybe your own pictures of crazy fashion, you can
如果你们有其他建议，或者自己拍的疯狂时尚照片，也可以上传。
post.
上传。
We're glad to see them.
我们很乐意看到。
So we'll see you guys there.
那我们网站上见。
Yeah.
是的。
As Marco said, hope to see you on the website.
就像马可说的，希望能在网站上见到你们。
That's about it for today.
今天就到这里。
So goodbye, everyone.
所以，大家再见。
Bye.
再见。